{
    "subject": "resource/Akira_Tohei",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Japanese_aikidoka",
    "human_readable": "Akira Tohei is a subject of Category:Japanese aikidoka.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8614072799682617,
            "question": "Is there a specific style or school of aikido associated with Akira Tohei?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8349589705467224,
            "question": "Are there any famous Japanese aikidokas besides Akira Tohei?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7159096002578735,
            "question": "What is Akira Tohei known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7058032155036926,
            "question": "How did Akira Tohei contribute to the field of aikido?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6732542514801025,
            "question": "Where is Akira Tohei from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6639662384986877,
            "question": "What does it mean to be a Japanese aikidoka?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6123946309089661,
            "question": "What is the significance of being a Japanese aikidoka in terms of culture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2735764980316162,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about aikido?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25239092111587524,
            "question": "How has aikido influenced Japanese martial arts traditions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1845410168170929,
            "question": "What are some of the principles of aikido practice?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Akira Tohei is a subject of Category:Japanese aikidoka.",
            "html": "dbpedia_658_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has aikido influenced Japanese martial arts traditions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_658_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about aikido?",
            "html": "dbpedia_658_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of being a Japanese aikidoka in terms of culture?",
            "html": "dbpedia_658_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_658_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_658_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_658_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_658_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_658_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_658_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_658_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_658_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_658_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_658_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n**Explanation:**\n\nThe text states that Akira Tohei was an Aikido instructor and a direct disciple of Morihei Ueshiba, the founder of Aikido. This strongly suggests he would be considered a Japanese aikidoka. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents contain information about Akira Tohei, including his birthdate, martial art background, and role as an instructor in Aikido. The text also mentions that he was a Shihan (8th Dan) and had taught at the Midwest Aikido Center for many years. This supports the statement that Akira Tohei is a subject of Category:Japanese aikidoka."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Akira Tohei's significant contributions to Aikido, including his rank (8th degree black belt or 8th Dan), his role as a chief instructor in the Midwest Aikido Center, and his influence on the dissemination of Aikido. This information supports that Akira Tohei is indeed a subject categorized under Japanese Aikidoka."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}